Easiest way to 200K likes.
Get ready with me for my first
date in three years.
Here's everything I eat
in a day as a ballet dancer.
Get the fuck outta here!
I make my own coin!
How can you be certain
about anything?
How much do you pay for rent?
You are making me feel
very unsafe!
When you accidentally
charge underwear
to your company credit card.
Aah!
Crazy bitch!
Everywhere you turn,
everywhere you look,
no matter where you are,
it is a war zone.
You can't even walk...
Oh!
I just don't want...
Take 'em off, take 'em off.
I decided to include this
sequence in my study
for it portrayed a barbaric
method of dealing
with the criminal.
The one redeeming factor of
holding a public execution is
perhaps it is a deterrent
to crime.
- Hey.
- What's up?
So there's a new team
orientation tomorrow,
and I'm supposed to walk
the newbies through it,
but I'm swamped.
And so I was wondering
if maybe you could cover for me.
Awesome. Yeah.
Um... sure I can lead it?
Like, is that allowed?
Yeah.
This is the perfect opportunity
for you to prove yourself.
Okay.
Oh. Get back to it.
- Mm-hmm.
Perhaps it is
a deterrent to crime.
- Bye, Ed.
- See you, Margot.
Have a good one.
Oh. Wearing your steel-toed
boots again, huh?
Come on back.
Come on back to see me.
- Sorry, I forgot.
- Mm-hmm.
What company secrets
are you stealing today, Margot?
- Ah. New painting. Nice.
- Thanks.
I got spicy pickles.
Yeah, baby.
How was traumatic hell job?
Good. Josh gave me
some new responsibilities.
Cool, cool.
Could be pretty close
to a promotion.
No way!
- Yeah.
- That's great.
Feel like I could be making
real difference.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe you
like this shit.
It's a classic.
So
um, question.
Yeah?
Would you possibly
maybe...
wanna to come to Cassidy's
with me tonight?
She's just having a chill,
small kind of...
housewarming party thing.
Uh...
I don't know.
You know, I've got,
like, laundry and stuff.
Oh, come on. Come on.
Remember what we talked about?
Getting back out into the world.
You know...
seeing friends again.
I miss my best friend.
Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm, hmm?
You know what?
Yeah.
Let's go.
- Oh, yes.
Yes. Mwah!
It's gonna be fun.
- Yeah.
You excited?
Yeah.
This thing's, like, impossible.
Oh. Here. Try this.
A lipstick?
Wah. A knife.
Sha-sha!
It's conceptual art.
- It's cool. Ow.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
So, is tying a cherry stem with
your tongue, like, a real thing?
Or just, like, a lesbian thing?
Voilà!
Wait. That's so hot.
Ryan, don't!
- Oh, my God.
- I'm offline for a reason.
I wasn't even gonna post it.
Oh, wait. Cassidy said
she wanted whipped cream.
Do you think we need
whipped cream?
- I think that's the girl.
- Is whipped cream gauche?
- No.
- Yes, it is. 100% positive.
- What? What?
- That's definitely her.
Are those girls watching me?
It's definitely her.
I gotta say something.
I think they're just
checking you out.
That's the train girl.
- I'm gonna say something.
I'm gonna say something,
I'm gonna do it.
Hey, are you the girl
from that train video?
- Fuck.
- I shouldn't have even tried.
Margot, wait! Margot, wait!
She probably just liked it.
Hey, sis.
Happy 23rd birthday!
I hope that this is the year
that you finally get
a girlfriend
so you can stop bugging
me all the time.
Okay? I love you so much.
I'll see you tonight. Bye.
Hey. Happy Thanksgiving.
I'm running late.
I forgot literally everything.
I left your dress at home.
But I promise I'm gonna grab it
so you can wear it, but...
Margot!
Okay, I love you.
And you're the best sister
in the world.
So, okay, see you soon.
Here at Kino Moderation,
this is who we protect.
The young, the impressionable,
the innocent.
When you come across content
that violates policy,
flag it and move on.
You may be tempted to look
into it outside of work,
but that is a violation
of your NDA.
Don't discuss it.
Don't Google it.
Don't even think about it,
if you can help it.
Okay.
Hmm. Burnout.
Hey.
Don't worry. It's not tobacco.
No, thank you, I'm good.
I just feel
like we have a responsibility
to keep our heads clear.
If I kept a clear head, I'd
blow it clear across the office.
Then why do you work here?
Because it's a thrill...
when you get a really good one.
Plus, they have dental.
Are you gonna finish that?
Here, kitty, kitty.
Meow, meow.
How to save a life, part two.
So this is Naloxone,
a.k.a. Narcan.
And it works by blocking the
opiate receptors in your brain.
Now, while Narcan should
not be used prophylactically...
it is really excellent
at reversing
and stopping an overdose.
Aah!
But when the guards led him
down death row
toward the execution chamber,
he seemed nervous
and totally disoriented.
I began to wonder if
two wrongs really make a right.
No.
His eyes are taped
to prevent them
from popping out
of their sockets.
The next step is the flick
of a switch,
which sends a current
of 2,000 volts
through the victim's body.
And the whole process
is repeated
as many times as necessary
until the prisoner
is proclaimed dead
by the physician on duty.
The room began to smell
like burning flesh.
The final trickle of blood
marked the conclusion
to this grotesque execution.
But when the guards led him
down death row
toward the execution chamber...
- What's up?
Um...
...wondering if two
wrongs really make a right.
I'm not sure what
to do with this one.
I saw another video
just like this a few days ago.
Mannequins and... a beheading.
I thought it wasn't real, but...
he looks like
he's actually dying in this.
Like, I don't know,
it's made to look stylized
so we don't flag it.
But do you think
this could be,
like, a real execution?
I don't know.
Leave it up.
Josh, again...
I saw another video
just like this, it's...
DIY horror's
trafficking right now.
Support the trend.
What do we say?
Give the people what they want.
Hey, you're still on
for the lake, right?
Yeah. I'm coming.
- Alright.
- Popping out of their sockets.
But the next step is
the flick of a switch,
which sends a current
of 2,000 volts
through the victim's--
Train's coming!
Come with me
to get my--
Oh, God! Yes, bro!
Oh! Oh!
This is how you manipulate
algorithms like a pro.
Okay, listen. You...
Hello.
We need to talk about fame.
Guys, I think I'm gonna
have to drop out of school.
It's gotten to the point now
where I can't go anywhere
without being recog--
My boyfriend is
coming over today...
The best water bottle
I have ever used...
This is the final look.
Where are you, Sammy?
Where are you?
Hey, Arthur.
Bathroom's all clean.
So, can I go?
- Sure thing, bud.
- Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
- ♪ You follow me
- ♪ Everybody knows I
- ♪ Everybody knows
♪ You follow me
♪ You know
you can't ignore this ♪
Oh, my God!
Dude, you scared me.
Okay, come on.
Let's shoot.
Alright. Perfect.
Sam, it's--
it's really public.
Yeah, but at the pool,
you can be in a swimsuit
without
the video getting flagged.
Facts. Okay. Okay.
Let's do it.
- Noodle time. Bl-bl-bl-bl.
- What the fuck?
- Really?
- Seriously?
People have nothing better
to do
than disturb people
who are trying to fucking work.
- Just start it over.
- They're obsessed with us.
It's so fucking annoying.
Whatever.
Okay.
Hey!
We need to talk about fame.
Guys, I think I'm gonna
have to drop out of school.
It's gotten to the point now
where I can't go anywhere...
Is someone here?
...without being recognized
at least once.
The other day, I was in class
and I looked over to my left
and this girl was taking
a video of me
while I was taking an exam.
Is anybody here?
I mean,
how am I supposed to focus
if someone's watching
my every single move?
Make sure to blend
and powder immediately after.
Otherwise, you're gonna crease.
I started this account
because I genuinely
wanted to give advice
and share my tips and tricks,
but now it's just starting
to feel like everyone's
forgetting
that I'm a real person.
But I'm very grateful to have
this amount of exposure
and to get to be a role model,
especially for young girls
that look up to me.
But I just want to be
normal sometimes, you know?
I just feel like
with all this new pressure,
I have to kind of put on a face
all the time and--
Is this some sort of joke?
'Cause it isn't funny.
This isn't fucking funny.
This is literally harassment.
Fucking idiots.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Help! Help!
So it's always a good time
to talk about condoms.
You want to pinch the tip
of the condom
and put it on the head
of the penis.
From the moment
patrons enter these premises,
they are treated like royalty.
Secured in a special trap,
the animal was now ready
to become the main dish.
No!
Following a few
simple instructions,
the men at the table
were prepared for the kill.
After a matter of seconds,
the gruesome ritual had ended.
The skull was carved open
for the delicate brains inside.
While this continued,
it occurred to me
that within the confines
of this elegant restaurant,
people were paying
exorbitant prices
to play the role of a hunter.
When I asked a man
with a hearty appetite
why he enjoyed the meal,
he replied,
"If I can get closer to God
by eating brains, why not?"
Hey, food's up!
♪ I've got a feeling
Hey, Mar-go-rita!
- Hello!
- Lake life! Lake life!
Excuse me, dude.
This looks good.
Yeah.
Last time I had some,
I lost my wedding ring
in them motherfuckers, man.
For real.
- Damn.
- Alright, man. Thanks.
- Good to see you, brother.
I saw
another mannequin video.
No.
Margot, we're not working today.
But I saw this man,
got his head bashed in.
He was scalped.
- Come here.
No, like, it was horrible.
Stop.
Come on.
We can't talk about it here,
and you know that.
I can't get your attention
at the office.
And we need to escalate.
Escalating to law enforcement
brings negative attention
to the platform.
What if someone dies?
Are you gonna feel good
about company policy?
You know what your weakness is?
You take this work
too personally.
What if this is
just one creator?
I mean, high-quality footage,
mannequins,
elaborate death, I mean,
we could at least take it
offline.
Do we look like
the morality police?
It's censorship, and
you know I hate the "C" word,
but censorship is
a slippery slope.
What if lives are at stake?
I mean--
Margot. Do you sound manic?
No, I'm not!
Dude, I'm not crazy.
You begged me for this job,
and I vouched for you.
Even with your history,
I said that you can handle it.
I said you had a reason
to be here,
so please don't let me down.
Don't let yourself down, either.
You can't fix everything.
- Right.
- Lake life!
Lake life!
Margot! Margot!
It's too dangerous.
That's kinda the point.
Alright, the train's coming!
The train's coming!
No!
- Margot!
- Aah!
I decided to include
this sequence in my study
for it portrayed
a barbaric method
of dealing with the criminal.
The one redeeming factor
of holding a public execution
is perhaps
it is a deterrent to crime.
But when the guards led him
down death row
toward the execution chamber,
he seemed nervous,
totally disoriented.
Sorry to bother you. I watch
your show every morning.
Can I get a picture?
- Yeah, sure.
Aw, shit!
You alright?
I-- I cut myself.
You need a hand?
Ha ha. You, uh,
you got a new one?
No, come on.
I can get you a bandage.
I just gotta find these things.
I don't know
where Lisa keeps 'em.
I just gotta find them.
Ahh, here.
There we go.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
I'm Neal, by the way.
I'm, um, I'm Francis.
Well, you live around here?
My girlfriend does,
a few houses up, actually.
Oh, really? What's her name?
I'm sure I know her.
Her name is Claire.
The tall girl.
Claire, the tall girl.
Yeah, that's Claire.
Very tall.
Huh. Well, hey, neighbor.
You want a beer?
- I'd love a beer.
I gotcha.
Heads up.
- Oh.
- Oh. Sorry.
- Oh! No, I caught it.
- Nice!
- Ha ha.
Ahh.
What, uh, what kind of business
are you in?
I make videos.
- What, like, movies?
- Yeah.
You use that Kino app
for smartphone?
My kids are on it.
Lot of important stuff on
there, you know?
What do you mean?
Oh, you know, the zeitgeist.
Oh, my gosh.
Is that an award?
- Yeah, I work in television.
Dad.
Can I have it back now?
30 minutes.
Well, thanks a lot.
You have yourself
a great Sunday.
Thanks, Neal.
- Your hand okay?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks again.
Let's see how we did.
A Jacksonville woman's
tragic last moments
have been circulating
on social media
after she leapt from the roof
of an apartment building.
In this dramatic footage,
we see first responders
attempting to drag her
to safety.
Unfortunately, attempts failed
and she ultimately plummeted
to her death.
Authorities have been unable to
determine the woman's identity.
Meanwhile, Yoko the puppy...
...brought joy to the seniors
at Marshwood
Community Center...
Drew?!
...which intends to foster
puppies through the same org--
God damn it.
Huh.
Jesus Christ.
Drew, did you plug your Xbox
into that outlet again?
Huh.
Drew. What the fuck?!
Jesus!
What the...
Hey!
What? Fuck!
Dad?
Dad, is everything okay?
Dad? Dad! What--
Dad, what happened?
Dad, wake up!
Shit! Hold on,
I'm calling for help, okay?
Aah!
Why does this have
so many views?
- What are you watching?
- Wanna see?
It's wild.
Someone keeps reposting it.
Seriously? This isn't funny.
Someone could actually
be dying in that.
Who cares?
It's called coping.
I mean,
we're all going to Hell anyway.
No!
Whoa, what the fuck?
Give me back my phone.
This is fucked up.
This is a person.
Yeah, well,
riding your high horse
isn't gonna bring anyone
back to life.
Oh, shit.
Is it gonna stop you
from being such a fucking cunt?
- Jesus.
- Margot!
- Hey.
I'm Dr. Francis Gross.
I work as a pathologist
and over the past 20 years,
I've compiled a library
with many faces of death.
My travels have taken
me all--
...will soon begin the ritual
which brought them here.
Waiters signal
for the house specialty.
As the monkey was brought
down the hall
and a toast to prosperity
was made,
the waiter presented the men
with their tools
of destruction.
Secured in a special trap,
the animal was now ready
to become the main dish.
Following a few
simple instructions,
the men of the table
were prepared for the kill.
That's all I have to do?
After a matter of seconds,
the gruesome ritual had ended.
The skull was carved--
...conscious and
the whole process is repeated
as many times as necessary
until the prisoner
is proclaimed dead
by the physician on duty.
The room began to smell--
Howdy, babes.
I thought you were
on a date.
Uh, yeah, I mean, he was cool.
I just felt a little sick
after dinner, so I left early.
That's my laptop.
What you doing?
Ryan, what is "Faces of Death"?
Oh, my God. "Faces of Death"?
It's a classic.
But that one actually
kind of fucked me up.
- Is it, like, a documentary?
- Kinda.
It's, like, this
totally cursed tape.
This doctor is showing
a super-dark collection
of footage
of people dying
in different ways.
It's giving
"Blockbuster night manager
hides it in his safe
under his desk with the pornos."
You know that you had to
actually bribe him
to even rent it.
It was like the first
viral video
before the Internet invented
viral videos.
But the craziest part is...
none of it was real.
Which, honestly,
pissed a lot of people off.
Anyway, why do you even care?
You hate this shit.
Hold on.
Let me show you something
...toward the execution
chamber,
he seemed nervous
and totally disoriented.
I began to wonder
if two wrongs
really make a right.
- What is this?
Ryan...
I've been seeing these videos
at work, right?
Like, people report them.
I think that someone's, like,
really killing people
and copying this movie.
Babe, that was the whole point.
With "Faces,"
people thought it was real,
but it was just
super-believable gore.
Ryan, I think it's real
and there's a fucking psycho
out there.
- How would you know that?
- He is missing
and then he shows up
in the video.
Look at this one.
...marked the conclusion
to this grotesque execution.
I began to wonder
if two wrongs...
God.
Did you tell someone
at work?
Yeah, and they think
I'm overreacting.
They won't do shit.
Then maybe you should
just go to the cops.
There is not enough info
to go to the cops.
They're gonna go
straight to Kino
and Kino is gonna fire my ass
and then maybe even sue me.
Ryan, I need to do something.
Something? What, are you gonna
go full "Don't Fuck with Cats"?
I mean...
If I can get my hands
on the original HD files,
I can run an analysis
on the metadata,
even maybe find out
where he lives.
And then Josh has to believe me,
or even the cops.
Margot, I was kidding.
Right. No, me too.
Can I borrow your
lipstick knife?
I didn't forget this time.
- Look at you.
Hey, Josh.
Yo.
- Hi.
- What it do?
You're a Dead fan, right?
- Damn. What?
- You're a Dead fan?
Oh. Yeah, I'm a Deadhead.
So  I realized how much
you've been doing for me,
you know, getting me this job
and putting up with my shit
and...
So I got you these.
Thought you could take Chelsea.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh. Shit.
How'd you get these?
Damn.
This is for tonight's show?
Mm-hmm.
Man, I got this audit conform.
I'm gonna be late.
- Oh, shoot. Is that now?
- Mm. Yeah.
Or maybe, you know,
I could do it for you.
Fuck it.
I can break a couple of rules.
- Sweet.
- I am the boss. Alright?
What, you want to work here?
- Yeah, I figure that's easiest.
Okay, but you'll need access
to the database.
Get you all set up.
So listen,
if you get stuck on anything,
I'll just handle it tomorrow.
- Cool.
But there is
another kind of killer--
the human being who murders
for no apparent reason.
This person is placed
in a situation
where violence
is the only means
of dealing with reality.
There are no judgments
or morals behind the crime.
It is an eruption of repression
that manifests itself
by causing the death
of others.
After several hours,
Lawrence's one-man revolt
was finally defeated.
But Lawrence was
not the only victim
that died
on that summer afternoon.
Stop it.
I said stop it.
If you don't make noise,
then you don't get hurt.
Shh.
And now... we eat.
Hmm?
Want a bit of pizza?
Come here.
Hmm. That's it.
Yeah.
- Please don't.
- Ooh. Come on.
Mm.
- No.
Come on.
Ahh.
So good.
You know...
you should be more grateful.
I know
how much you wanna be famous.
Everyone's talking about you.
What are-- What are--
What are they saying?
They're asking questions,
Sammy.
They want to know more.
And we are going to give
them more.
That is the first rule
of content creation.
Give the people what they want.
Come on, Neal.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
No!
Ohh.
People love this shit, Neal.
But... we only get one shot.
Huh?
So...
...you're gonna have to
give it everything you've got.
I would hate
to have to recast your role.
Yeah. Get angry, Neal!
They like it when you get angry.
Yeah.
You wanna shoot me?
Yeah, you do.
Here you go.
Come on.
Do it. I dare you.
Huh.
Don't you want to get
outta here, Neal?!
Huh?!
Come on!
Just blow my fuckin' brains out.
And...
action!
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Really great work, Neal.
Look at you, Neal.
Ugh!
- What are you doing?
- I'm looking for the originals.
Hey, guys, I fucked a clown,
and I got VV.
- From the moment patrons...
- Yes!
- What?
- Got it.
...they are treated like
royalty.
Yikes.
Now to see what
the Internet knows.
Margot, don't you think
this is a little irresponsible?
Weren't you the one
who told me to go full on
Don't Fuck with Cats?
- I said I was joking!
I wasn't.
Hmm.
Oh, my God.
- What?
The guy
in the electrocution video
disappeared from the same area.
The Internet... is fast.
I knew it.
This is...
This is so bad.
They think that she's
just missing like the other guy.
Yeah, damn, bitch.
We should get some reward money.
Ryan, can you not?
This is serious.
This girl could be in danger.
Okay, but I think you
need to take it easy on this.
You know, it really seems
like you're spinning out.
Like, are you taking
pills again?
Justin Podd is a filmmaker.
This girl Sam is big on Kino.
They're both kind of famous.
This cannot be a coincidence!
Well, this is also
low-key scary.
And we shouldn't get caught up
in this.
- Then who should?
- I don't know!
Maybe someone
who isn't on my laptop?
Ryan, I'm allowed
to post online
in my own house!
- Okay, we're done!
- No! My hard drive!
- I'm sorry.
What the hell are you doing?
What was that?
- This is freaking me out!
I don't want you using
my laptop anymore.
- It's too dangerous.
- That's kinda the point.
Train's coming!
Hmm.
Let's go!
- So, this is from a website?
- Yeah.
Kino, it's an app.
The guy in the video
disappeared
and there's a girl Sam,
also from Jacksonville,
also is missing.
I have the originals,
and they have the metadata.
So, that should be enough
to know who posted it
or at least that it's
coming from the same source.
So, there's a guy
who disappeared
and an unrelated girl
in another state?
I need a homicide
to investigate a homicide.
Bodies, crime scenes...
Yeah, but, I mean, there's
more. It's a pattern.
I mean, it's all based
off this old horror movie
called "Faces of Death."
Right. Right.
You're Margot Romero,
aren't you?
You think I'm making this up?
I mean, it's all a very...
fantastic tale.
Right.
Margot. Hey.
Been trying to call you.
So, listen, it sucks
that I have to do this,
but you crossed the line.
And I'm left with no choice.
About what? How?
You left these in my office.
- Okay, but...
- Fuckin' stimulants?
Again?
Everyone takes something
to get them through the day.
You're not everyone!
Not only did you break company
policy, but you broke my trust.
Josh, you broke mine.
You need to listen to me
about these videos.
I have evidence!
There is a person...
- You're done.
I don't know why you're making
a scene, but you're done.
I don't have a choice.
- You do have a choice!
You have the choice
to take your job seriously!
Key card.
You know what?
I don't need this.
And you're gonna see
you fucked up, Josh!
You'll see.
- Margot!
You should talk to somebody.
Shut up, Josh! Asshole!
And for your sake, I hope
you remember you signed an NDA!
There is
another kind of killer--
the human being who murders
for no apparent reason.
This person is placed
in a situation
where violence is the only
means of dealing with reality.
Hey, can I talk to you
for a sec?
What's up?
You got a computer.
Josh fired me.
Oh.
You okay?
It's fine.
Job was bullshit anyway.
Come on.
You don't believe that.
What happened?
Look, after...
after I made Sophie film
that video with me,
after the cops leaked it,
I thought,
"Okay, maybe
if I do my part
and try to clean up the
Internet, then it'll be fine."
Right?
But Kino doesn't give a shit.
They don't care.
No one cares.
It's like we watch this shit
for... entertainment
and we forget
that these are real people
with lives and, like, families,
and they're not just, like,
a digital fucking image.
Right? Like...
I have to do this.
This is real, like,
real people are dying.
And if I can prove it,
then...
maybe Sophie's death
wasn't for nothing.
Maybe something good
can come out of it.
Just be careful.
I care about you
and if anything happened to you,
I...
It'd be really annoying.
Okay, I'll try my best.
I'll save you some pizza.
Shut up!
Rawwr!
Get off of me!
Get off!
No!
Margot!
Margot! Help! Help!
Margot! Margot!
Ryan?
What was that?
Rawr!
Let's go!
Sophie!
Train's coming!
Let's go!
Amateur Internet sleuths
have compiled evidence
of what they claim
might be real snuff films
circulating online.
The animal was now ready
to become the main dish.
No!
The videos themselves
have spawned
countless disturbing
and violent imitations,
leading to concerns
that future copycat videos
may become more extreme
and potentially even deadly.
It has come to my attention
that those [bleep]
death videos are real.
Do not watch these videos.
If you keep watching
these videos,
they will make more of them,
and they will spread.
Kino spokesperson Valon Mendez
issued this statement.
Kino is committed
to the safety
and welfare of our community.
All content
that violates our guidelines
is promptly removed
from the platform.
She goes on to say, "We
respect our users' privacy
and rights to free speech."
Train coming!
Let me see.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm Margot.
Okay.
Oh. Oh.
Come here. Come here.
Thank you so much.
- Come here. I'm here to help.
- He'll come back.
We have to go now.
- Who? Who is he?
- I don't know.
Is he making videos?
Have you seen anything?
- I don't know. We have to go.
- Please. Please!
Anything, please!
- No, no, no.
Just tell me anything.
Wait. Wait.
- Hurry, please.
No! Oh, no!
It's gonna be okay.
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
Let's go. Let's go!
Let's go, let's go.
I find this kind of death
particularly tragic.
It's caused by sheer stupidity.
Often, we do things
which later we regret.
Through situations
such as this,
I am further able to understand
the fine line
between life and death.
When it is a person's time
to die,
the forces of nature
have little discrimination.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- We have to go.
- We need evidence.
- I amevidence.
Evidence of the videos.
Margot!
We have to go!
Fuck.
Margot.
Margot!
Come on!
Margot! Fuck it.
Help! Help! Help!
Help! Help!
Help!
- Zigzag, Sammy!
Zigzag!
- Fuck.
Help!
Help! Help!
Fuck. Fucking idiots.
Help! No! Help!
Okay.
Aah!
No!
Sam!
Aah!
Fuck.
Blahhhh!
No.
No, no, no.
Wait.
Your call cannot be completed
as dialed.
No, no, no, no.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Get down!
- Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Get in the car.
Please.
You have to help me.
No!
No! Please!
Ah!
What's your emergency?
Hello. Hello.
Hello? Hello?
Ma'am, are you there?
Yeah. I'm here.
Yes,
this is emergency services.
How can I help you?
No!
- Hello?
Ma'am, are you there?
911. What's your emergency?
Hi.
Uh, my name is Arthur Spevak,
and I want to report
an incident.
Oh. Keep going,
keep-- keep going.
It's this one right here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
So this is the house?
Looks familiar?
Yeah.
I-I only saw it from the back.
Just stay here.
We're gonna go talk to him,
and you let us know
if you recognize him.
Alright?
- Okay.
Unit 1124,
we received a 1498 from
the resident at Hilton Court.
A Caucasian female
in a blue floral shirt.
Trespassing.
Copy that.
Miss, wait here.
Just a second.
Jacksonville PD.
Open up.
Oh, officers.
Oh, I am so relieved to see you.
Oh, no.
What's she doing here?
That woman is disturbed.
She's obsessed with me.
She keeps--
She keeps accusing me of keeping
people tied up in my basement.
Do you live here alone, sir?
Is there anyone else
in the house currently?
No, it's-- it's just me.
I mean,
it was my parents' house,
but, uh, recently they passed.
Train accident.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
Do you know
why we're here today?
Well, I assume
because I called you about her.
Sir, this woman claims
she was held against her will
at this location.
Listen, officers,
I am so happy to cooperate.
But this isn't the first time
she has shown up making
false accusations about me.
You get it.
She just wants my attention.
- He's lying!
- Miss, you need to step back!
- Officer, please. Please.
- I am not gonna ask you again.
Step back to the sidewalk.
Please. Just go inside.
I'm standing here
covered in blood,
telling you this man is
killing people.
Alright. Relax, relax.
Just go inside
the fucking house!
- Step back. I won't ask again.
- Just go inside, please.
- Officers.
- Sir, we don't need your help.
- She has had a hard time.
- Sir--
You understand?
She killed her own sister.
- You're the fucking killer!
- Let him go!
- Hey! Let go!
- You're the killer!
- Let him go!
- Let me go!
Get the fuck off of me!
You know, I just want her
to get the help that she needs.
Anyway, I won't
be pressing charges.
Have a great day
and thanks for coming by.
- Sir, that'll be enough.
- I really appreciate it.
You proud of me, Sammy?
Did I do good?
Putting on a show for the pigs.
I am inspired.
You have freed me.
Given me true artistic license.
And people have always
criticized me my entire life.
They think they know what
I'm capable of,
but they haven't seen
anything yet.
Come on, come on.
- Oh!
- Come on!
There we go.
The police said you had
a mental-health crisis.
What happened?
I was running
from a serial killer.
Well, whatever it was, it's...
It's got to hurt.
Your blood tests showed
fentanyl in your system.
Are you having trouble
with drugs or alcohol?
I can make you an appointment
with a social worker
who can find you a longer-term
treatment for your addiction.
I'm not an addict!
We've instituted
a new harm reduction protocol.
Do you know
how to administer Narcan?
Are you ready, Sammy?
It's showtime.
Fucked up.
Yeah.
Apparently,
he's posting a new one tonight.
Yeah.
I'm obsessed.
Have you seen
the original movie thing?
Yeah. "Faces."
It's iconic.
But there is
another kind of killer.
The human being who murders
for no apparent reason.
This person is placed
in a situation
where violence
is the only means
of dealing with reality.
I hate to ask this, but...
do I know you from somewhere?
You mean the train video?
Is that you?
Yep.
That's me.
Man, that's fucked up.
Hey, Margot.
Welcome to my home.
Where's the drive?
Somewhere secure.
Where?
When I know everyone is safe,
I'll tell you.
Empty your pockets.
What's that?
It's lipstick.
Show me.
Gotta look sharp.
In the corner.
Go on.
Go on, go on.
Would you say you like my work?
- What?
- Are you a fan of my work?
Sure. I'm a fan.
So you get it, then?
Get what?
When I found out you were
Train Girl, I thought to myself,
"Now, shereally gets it."
People love me, Margot.
Kino loves me.
The news and advertisers
love me.
The gun companies and
home-security companies
and the government loves me.
I mean, you saw.
Even the cops love me.
It is the attention economy
and, baby, business is booming.
- Why "Faces"?
- What?
Why "Faces of Death"?
Why that movie?
Because
the algorithm loves remakes.
People love remakes.
If it is a remake,
well, you can get away
with murder. Hmm.
And "Faces" is funny.
People like funny shit, right?
I came here for Sam
and the kid.
If you insist.
Garage.
Keep going.
You know, you really
should be more grateful.
You are a part of the future.
Go on.
To the left.
That's it.
Open it.
We are going to live forever.
Sam?
Sam?!
Where is she?
It's not exactly canon.
I took some creative license.
You like it?
- Aah!
What?! No!
Oh!
What did you do?
- Such a little cuck, Margot.
Like, how dumb are you?
You can't hurt me.
People know where I am.
I don't want to hurt you.
I want to work with you.
I don't want to
have to shoot you.
I want you to go out
with some flair.
No. Please, please, please,
please, please.
- Hmm.
- Please.
Go. Go.
Please, please, please.
No!!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I don't have all day, Margot.
Shit is starting to smell.
Please, please, please, don't.
Please.
Ple--
See?
Was that so hard?
What do you think, Sammy?
You think it's gonna resonate, hmm?
What do you think
of our magnum opus?
You know, Margot...
...your sister was a real face
of death.
And now...
you are going to join her.
Immortalized.
Hmm.
It's like a real family business
with you guys.
Honestly... I'm jealous.
Now let's get to it.
No!
No.
Aah!
Narcan.
I have your confession.
My name is Margot Romero,
a.k.a. Train Girl.
And this is Arthur Spevak.
Nobody would listen to me.
But now you will.
Because what do they say?
Give the people what they want.
This is so much better.
Shut up!
I realize that when we die,
it really isn't the end.
Somehow I feel the soul
in each of us
remains a traveler forever.
During the past 20 years,
I know that my compulsion
to understand death
was much greater
than just an obsession.
My dreams had dictated
my mission.
To discover a circle
that forever repeats itself.
The end of the beginning
or the beginning of the end?
I'll leave that decision
to you.
I realize that when we die,
it really isn't the end.
Somehow I feel the soul in
each of us--
The moment death occurs,
my expertise is called upon.
Was plagued
with the many faces of death.
My travels have taken me
all over the world,
searching for
the various situations
that have dealt with
our ultimate enemy.
I've seen with my own eyes
a myriad of experiences
that have led me
to a greater awareness
of the living.
We have developed a world
that refuses
to recognize our own destiny,
displayed with the many faces
of death.
During the past 20 years,
I know that my compulsion
to understand death
is much greater
than just an obsession.
My dreams have dictated
my vision.
Now it is time
to witness the final moment.
To discover a circle
that forever repeats itself.
The end of the beginning
or the beginning of the end?
I'll leave that decision to
you.